penatropin.com 2016-10-28

# Penatropin | Official Website

###### Registration

Registration at penatropin.com is not required. However, during checkout you will be required to provide contact information (such as name, email address, billing and shipping address). We use your information to send you an order confirmation and shipping notification for your order.

Phyto Health USA, LLC is the sole owner of the information collected on penatropin.com. Phyto Health USA, LLC collects personally identifiable information from our users during check out.

###### Orders

If you purchase a product from us, we request certain personally identifiable information from you on our order form. You must provide contact information (such as name, email, and shipping address) and financial information (such as credit card number, expiration date). We use this information for billing purposes and to fill orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we will use this information to contact you.

###### Customer Service

Based upon the personally identifiable information you provide us, we will send you information regarding your order, shipment status and reorder promotions. We will also communicate with you in response to your inquiries, to provide the services you request. We will communicate with you by email or telephone, in accordance with your wishes.

###### Special Offers and Updates

We will occasionally send you information on products, services, special deals, and promotions. Out of respect for your privacy, we provide the option not to receive these types of communications. Please see the "Opt-out."

###### Newsletters

If you wish to subscribe to our newsletter(s), we will use your name and email address to send the newsletter to you. Out of respect for your privacy, we provide you a way to unsubscribe. Please see the "Opt-out" section.

###### Personally Identifiable Information

We do not share personally identifiable information with third parties in ways other than those disclosed within this privacy statement.

###### Tell A Friend Service

If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our affiliate program, we will ask you for your friend 's name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. Everest Nutrition does not store this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email.

Your friend may contact us Penatropin Customer Service to request that we remove this information from our database.

###### Agents

We use an outside shipping company (USPS, UPS, FedEx) to deliver orders and a credit card processing company to bill you for goods and services. These companies do not share or use personally identifiable information for any other purposes, and are prohibited from using your personally identifiable information for any other purposes.

###### Legal Disclaimer

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law, and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Website.

###### Log Files

As is true of most Websites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data.

We use this information with 3rd party web analytics and advertising companies when you visit our website. This information does not identify individual users, but is used to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users' movements around the site, and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole.

We do not link this automatically-collected data to personally identifiable information.

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user’s computer for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies on this site. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site.

We use persistent cookies. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser’s HELP file.

We set a persistent cookie to store your shipping address, so you don’t have to enter it more than once should you shop with us again. Persistent cookies also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site.

If you reject cookies, you may still use our site.

This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by Phyto Health USA, LLC and Penatropin only, and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

###### Links to Other Sites

This Website contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by Phyto Health USA, LLC. Please be aware that Phyto Health USA, LLC is not responsible for the privacy practices of these sites.

We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site to read the privacy statements of each and every Website that collects personally identifiable information.

This privacy statement applies only to information collected by this Website.

###### Security

The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card numbers) on our order forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL) before being sent over the Internet, We use SSL technology to prevent your information from being stolen or intercepted while being transferred to us. Your credit card information is always stored in encrypted form in a restricted-access database.

###### Access to Personally Identifiable Information

If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our products, you may correct, update, delete or deactivate it by emailing Penatropin Customer Support

###### Testimonials

We post customer testimonials on our web site which may contain personally identifiable information such as the customer's name. We obtain the customers' consent prior to posting their testimonials, and posting their names along with their testimonials.

###### Opt-Out

We provide you the opportunity to "opt-out" of having your personally identifiable information used for certain purposes when we ask for this information. For example, if you purchase a product but do not wish to receive any additional marketing material from us, you can indicate your preference by sending an email to Zenerx Customer Support.

If you no longer wish to receive our newsletter and promotional communications, you may opt-out by following the instructions included in each newsletter or communication, or by emailing us at Penatropin Customer Care.

###### Business Transitions

In the event Phyto Health USA, LLC goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your personally identifiable information will likely be among the assets transferred. You will be notified via notice on our Website for 30 days of any such change in ownership or control of your personal information.

###### Changes in this Privacy Statement

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, on the Penatropin homepage, and locations we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page.

###### Contact Us

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us. 

These statements have not been evaluated by the Food and Drug Administration and are for informational purposes only. They should not be considered medical advice. Always consult a doctor for medical advice. This product is not intended to diagnose, treat, cure, or prevent any disease. Penatropin is a registered trademark of Phyto Health USA.
